Just as you wished.
Consider this my gift to you.
ou think waving some cheap little
communication stone around is gonna scare me?
You’ve never touched the family business.
How would a failure like you
even know what we own?
What a disgrace to House Carter,
letting an ignorant failure speak here.
This trash should
be thrown out immediately.
The Carters don't need some miner.
Stop making a fool of yourself.
Get out! Get out of the Carter family!
In three days, I
will marry the Scott heiress.
At the Holy Cathedral.
I hope you’ll all attend.
Because this may be the only time
in your lives
you get to
witness something truly magnificent.
The Holy Cathedral?
Do you have any
idea what that place is?
It is the most sacred
site on all of Golantis.
Even kings and queens must reserve it
a year in advance.
A worthless miner like you
couldn’t even reach the front gates!
If he gets married in the holy church,
I'll crawl there on my knees.
Forget the holy church. He couldn't
even touch the outer wall.
All that mining must have
knocked his brains loose.
No need to humiliate him further.
He’s already lost everything.
All he has left
are these sad little
lies to prop
up his worthless pride.
Severin, what do you have left
besides empty pride?
In three days,
you'll know.
We going home.
My lord!
Every territory of House Carter
has come under heavy assault!